let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Who is the most powerful in One Punch Man?",
        answer: "Saitama",
        options: [
            "Genos",
            "Cosmic Garou",
            "Saitama",
            "Tatsumaki",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Who is Akira Toriyama?",
        answer: "The father of DBZ",
        options: [
            "The father of DBZ",
            "The father of Naruto",
            "A random person",
            "The father of JJK",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "In which manga do we hear 'Bankai'?",
        answer: "Bleach",
        options: [
            "Naruto",
            "Bleach",
            "Dragon Ball Z",
            "Jujutsu Kaisen",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Who is Natsu?",
        answer: "A wizard",
        options: [
            "A knight",
            "A clerk",
            "A kryptonian",
            "A wizard",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is 'jiki jiki no mi'?",
        answer: "A devil fruit",
        options: [
            "A devil fruit",
            "A magic sword",
            "A shield",
            "A town",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What is the main ability of the protagonist in 'My Hero Academia'?",
        answer: "One For All",
        options: [
            "Telekinesis",
            "Super strength",
            "Quirkless",
            "One For All",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "In 'Naruto,' what is the name of Naruto's signature move?",
        answer: "Rasengan",
        options: [
            "Rasengan",
            "Chidori",
            "Kamehameha",
            "Spirit Bomb",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Who is the author of the 'One Piece' manga?",
        answer: "Eiichiro Oda",
        options: [
            "Masashi Kishimoto",
            "Eiichiro Oda",
            "Akira Toriyama",
            "Yoshihiro Togashi",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What is the name of the main character in 'Attack on Titan'?",
        answer: "Eren Yeager",
        options: [
            "Eren Yeager",
            "Levi Ackerman",
            "Mikasa Ackerman",
            "Armin Arlert",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "In 'Death Note,' what is the name of the Shinigami who drops the Death Note?",
        answer: "Ryuk",
        options: [
            "Rem",
            "Ryuk",
            "Gelus",
            "Sidoh",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Which manga features the characters Guts and Griffith?",
        answer: "Berserk",
        options: [
            "Fullmetal Alchemist",
            "Berserk",
            "Fairy Tail",
            "Hunter x Hunter",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "What is the primary goal of the main character in 'Sword Art Online'?",
        answer: "To escape the game",
        options: [
            "To defeat all players",
            "To escape the game",
            "To become the strongest",
            "To find a rare item",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "In 'Dragon Ball Z,' who is Goku's main rival?",
        answer: "Vegeta",
        options: [
            "Vegeta",
            "Frieza",
            "Piccolo",
            "Cell",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "What is the name of the organization that opposes the main characters in 'Tokyo Ghoul'?",
        answer: "The CCG",
        options: [
            "The CCG",
            "The Akatsuki",
            "The Titans",
            "The Espada",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "In 'One Punch Man,' who is the main character known for defeating enemies with a single punch?",
        answer: "Saitama",
        options: [
            "Genos",
            "Saitama",
            "Mumen Rider",
            "Boros",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "Which manga features a world where people can manipulate elements through 'Alchemy'?",
        answer: "Fullmetal Alchemist",
        options: [
            "Fairy Tail",
            "Fullmetal Alchemist",
            "One Piece",
            "Black Clover",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "What is the name of the main female lead in 'Fruits Basket'?",
        answer: "Tohru Honda",
        options: [
            "Tohru Honda",
            "Kagome Higurashi",
            "Sakura Haruno",
            "Hinata Hyuga",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "In 'Demon Slayer,' what is the name of Tanjiro's sister?",
        answer: "Nezuko",
        options: [
            "Nezuko",
            "Shinobu",
            "Mitsuri",
            "Kanao",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "Which character in 'Bleach' wields a sword called Zangetsu?",
        answer: "Ichigo Kurosaki",
        options: [
            "Renji Abarai",
            "Ichigo Kurosaki",
            "Rukia Kuchiki",
            "Uryu Ishida",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "In 'Yu Yu Hakusho,' what is Yusuke Urameshi's spirit beast?",
        answer: "Puu",
        options: [
            "Hiei",
            "Kurama",
            "Puu",
            "Botan",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question: "What is the name of the main detective in 'Detective Conan'?",
        answer: "Shinichi Kudo",
        options: [
            "Shinichi Kudo",
            "Heiji Hattori",
            "Kaito Kuroba",
            "Ran Mouri",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "In 'Naruto,' what is the name of the village where Naruto is from?",
        answer: "Konohagakure",
        options: [
            "Sunagakure",
            "Konohagakure",
            "Kirigakure",
            "Iwagakure",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 23,
        question: "Which manga features a character named Monkey D. Luffy?",
        answer: "One Piece",
        options: [
            "One Piece",
            "Hunter x Hunter",
            "Naruto",
            "Bleach",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 24,
        question: "In 'Fairy Tail,' what is the name of the guild that Natsu belongs to?",
        answer: "Fairy Tail",
        options: [
            "Sabertooth",
            "Blue Pegasus",
            "Fairy Tail",
            "Grimoire Heart",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 25,
        question: "What is the main theme of 'Your Lie in April'?",
        answer: "Music and romance",
        options: [
            "Sports",
            "Music and romance",
            "Adventure",
            "Mystery",
        ]
    }
];
